Guide to the Ipas Records, 1965-2020; 1965-ongoing RL.00617
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Executive and Management Files, 1965-2014; 46 boxes
  - Ipas Clinic Loan application 75; org chart 87, instrument distribution 88-90, MVA marketing 89/90; UNICEF/UNIPAC ltrs 89-95; MVA project guidelines 90, infection prevention 92; Swedish SIDA 92-95; USAID 93-95; CAs mtg 94; PrepCom 93 & 94; ICPD 94; 4th World Conference on Women 95; Sally Shelton 95; approaches to training late 90s; Defining Reach 96; Snr staff retreat 96; safe abortion presentation 96; new issues 98; Khama Rogo 98; Strategic Planning Notebook 98; budgeting 99; matrix org structure 99-00; staff diversity 99-02; internal newsletters 00-01; results 05; Ipas history recap and timelines 01; planning 01; publications guide 02; Executive Team 02; internal survey 02; org charts 02-04; country team leader report 03; internal newsletters 03; strategic planning and budget cuts 03; "Rosa" Nicaragua 03; program review & budget issues 04; media 04-06, strategic plan 07-11; fundraising notebook 06; President's Messages to the Board of Directors 75-06 (Box 113)
  - Executive Files: MVA & Dilators 1976-2008 MVA history Battelle report 76; Denniston dilators 96-07; products and educational materials 91-95; FDA labeling/package insert 92; MVA trainers handbook 96 (notebook); marketing MVA 99-01; Ipas/PATH mtgs on cannulae 00-01; MVA redesign 02; MVA Plus training plan 02-03; MVA redesign 03; MVA sales/donations 03; MVA pricing 03-06; Morgan Lewis MVA plus 04; Denniston analysis 04; Romsons distribution agreement 04; romsons 04; EU regulatory data 05; PYXIS 05; Morgan Lewis clinician's guide 05; MVA Donawa Lifescience consulting 05-07; ISO 06; Biannual global PPD mtg 07 (notebook); Ipas distributor survey 06; HPSRx 06; MVA distribution 06-07; Selected clinical and programmatic literature on vacuum aspiration 08 (notebook); abortion technologies 07-08; MVA Curas consultancy 08 (Box 144)
  - Advances in Health Technology (AHT) 95-97 AHT mission statement 95; mife proposal 95; original proposal to Pop Council 95; methotrexate 95; Mife mtg June 95; AHT correspondence 95; AHT media and PR 95-96; AHT general 95-96; AHT public information 96; AHT incorporation 96; Pop Council/ Mife mtg NYC 96; Mife clinical research protocol 96; AHT/Ipas fiscal sponsorship 96; AHT chrono Jan-June 96; generic proposal 97; proposal for funding 97; PPFA methotrexate protocol 97; Mife NDA 96; AHT quarterly reports to Ipas 96-97; AHT chrono 97; AHT donor reports 97 (Box 145)
  - Executive Files 87-08, Ipas-Authored Articles, and Missing Ipas publications Early Ipas planning/reports/comms 87-95; RU-486 88-89; Romania trip report 90; Tbilisi presentation 91; abortion care in the developing world presentation 91; PAFP donor proposal 92; publications/general info 92-94; SIDA Bangladesh 93-94; unsafe abortion bibliography 96; sustainability paper 95; ICM trip report 96; Ipas country reports 96-97; Japan trip report and strategy 97-98; Japan corresp 97-00; activities to eliminate unsafe abortion 98?; Greenslade resignation 98; Myanmar 98; Info services/publications 98-02; journalists contacts 98-04; core support proposal 99; MVA tech transfer 99; strategic plan 99; EC mtg 99; Roe V Wade presentation 00; role of regional desks 00; Smith amendment 00; human rights case study 00; description of Ipas work 00; internal newsletter 01; Ipas overview presentation 01; Ipas history 01; DFID proposal 01; Essential RH references 01; WHO Safe abortion care workshop 02; presentations 02; franchising 02; Europe strategic planning 02; Ipas strategic directions 03; Ipas printed materials 95-03; Millenium project paper 05; Netherlands annual report 05; Indonesia 06; FIGO unsafe abortion working group 08 (Box 156)
  - Executive and Management files FY72-FY07: Intl Abortion Research Ctr Project 72, Henry David letter to E. Baulieu; Ipas library docs 92-94, Feedback internal newsletter 92-00; Interchange internal newsletter 92-98; board mtg notes 98; MA survey 01; MVA redesign presentation 01; Triangle Pop Society talk 01; Intl FP Coalition 01; Gag Rule 01; MA Task Force 01-02; Executive Team 01-02; Continuum of Care 01-05; Marie Bass 01-08; Board MA session 02; South Africa MA 02; MVA plus investigators mtg 02; Ipas activity map 02-05; Ipas newsletter 03; strategic directions 03; overview presentations 03; Concept Foundation 03-05; March for Women's Lives 04; R&E pubs list 04; Core donor reports and proposals 04-08; Ipas history country programs 05; Exec Team workplan 05; MA work 05; Gag Rule article by Barbara Crane 05; MVA redesign notes 05; MVA on-line 05; MVA redesign feedback and report 05-06; DFID MDG 5 06; Notes for donor visit 06; Eddie Mhlanga 06; Ipas training assessment 06; Background TSDI 06-07; ROI quality 06-07; M&E follow-up trainees 07; networks 07; OE outcomes report 07; Concept Foundation 07; M&E activities 07; strategic directions 07; staff photos 07; MA talk/tech session 07; Ipas Mex background paper 07; global pricing study 07; Presidents' messages to BOD 07-11, 1972-2007 (Box 191)
  - Executive and Management Files FY08-11: Exec Team retreat 08; MA 08; India consultant report MA 08; Planning 08; pay for performance 08; trainee retention lit review 08; products 08-09; Zizhu MDA data 09; PPD 08-09; Brazil agreement to legalize products 09; Exec Team 09; MA reference docs 09; abortion technology background 09; Exec Team retreats 09 (three folders); Scorecard/metrics 09; M&E issues 09; VCAT assessment 09; org issues 09; Brazil policy work 09; Ipas business model 09; UNPFA/MVA 09; Data PPD 09; Second trimester 09; Cost model RA1 09; country standards and guidelines 09; Tech updates to board 09; risk assessment 09-10; strategic planning 09-10; core donor documents 09-11; learning organizations 10; conflict resolution workshop 10; planning 10; Exec team retreat 10; DFID tender 10; strategic plan for 12-16 '10; Ops issues 10; directors strat planning meeting 10; Exec Team retreat 11; Core clinical content 11; Ghana CAC 11; reorg 11, 2008-2011 (Box 192)
  - WomanCare Global FY09-FY14: LLC formation 09; Ipas BOD mtg creation of WCG 09; creation of separate organization 09; intro of Saundra Pelletier 09; trademark name search 09; insurance applications 09-10; product line 09-10; updates to Ipas BOD 09-12; partnerships 09-12; overview presentations 09-12; evolution of WCG 09-12; Ipas Exec Comm mtg approval of LLC agreement; BOD mtg with H Vemer; MVA publications strategy 10; Dahua audit report 10; BOD mtg Oct 09 FY10; BOD mtg Nov 09 FY 10; BOD mtg Feb 10; BOD mtg April 10; Ipas approval of UK charity 10; global staff mtgs 10; LLC core team visit 10; NC LLC docs 10; business plan 10; misc comms 10-12; Simplant 10-11; BOD presentations 10-12; BOD members and rotation 10-12; staff org charts 10-13; severance pay plan 11; BOD mtg Aug 10 FY11; BOD mtg Oct 10 FY11; BOD mtg April 11; UK charity docs/comms 11; donor brochure 11; asset transfer agreement 11; structural changes 12; Ipas update for WCG board 12; WCG/Ipas comms 12; WCG/Ipas agreements 12; Mtgs of WCG entities 12; Linepharma 12; budgets/financials 12; Evofem background 12; BOD mtg Aug 11 FY12; BOT mtg Nov 11 FY12; BOD mtg May12; BOD presentation 12; documents WCGI/UK charity 12; WCG/Ipas service agreement 12; WCG update for Ipas BOD 13; L Maguire resignation from BOD 13; financial corresp 13; BOD financial update 13; Ipas/WCG mtg on MVA licensing 14; WCGI/Ipas joint mtg 14 (Box 196)
  - Liz Maguire 91-01: safe abortion background 91-99; article by Ipas staff 93; abortion stats 93-98; Mauritius unsafe abortion conf 94; PAC 94-99; Pop Council/PAC mtg 98; ltr NWPC 98; ltr Forrest Greensalde 98; MVA workshop presentation by K Beer 98; MVA sales 98-99; PROFIT project 98; USAID PAC 98-99; Rights and Technology in RH mtg 99; PAFP Turkey 99; fundraising 99; BOD rotations 99; announcement of LM as Ipas pres 99; EC 99; MA background 99; USAID PAC mtg 99; NYT article 99; PAC workshop presentations 99; JHPIEGO PAC workshop 99; comms with BOD 99-00; MA 99-02; Africa 99-03; LAC presentation to BOD 00; partnerships/networks 00; modeling mtg 00; gender/adol curriculum 00; Albania MVA training 00; Kenya/PRIME PAC 00; marketing presentation 00; EC mtg 00; DFID Bolivia 00; donor presentation 00; EC 00; FIGO history 00; midlevel providers 00; ab stats 00'; MVA re-design 00-01; corp officers 00-01; MA 00-01; MVA re-design 00-01; media 01; Med Comm technology discussion 01; BOD presentation 01; UNC School PH presentation 01; Funders Network presentation 01; Triangle Pop Society 01; PT/EC combo 01; briefing paper Turkey RH mtg 01; RH technologies BOD 01; Mexico visit 01; Gag Rule 01-02; Eurodonors 01-04; SIDA 01-05; core support Dutch 01-06; M&E 01-06, 1991-2001 (Box 197)
  - Liz Maguire 01-05: Comms audit 01-07; DFID 01-08; presentations by Ipas execs 01-11; new MVA donor presentation 02; USAID ltr on PAC 02; PAC conf Senegal 02; BOD MA discussion 02; Euromapping/IPPF 02; Francophone PAC 02; IT plan 02; Rights/refugees 02; Statement to UN Comm on Pop/Dev 02; Fjerstand ltr 02; workshop welcome 02; org structure changes 02; BOD presentation 02; UNFPA presentation 02; EuroNGO mtg 02; donor presentation 02; USAID PAC eval 02; R&E eval 02-03; Management team 02-03; Nepal 02-07; Mexico 02-08; org charts 02-09; Pres msg to BOD 03; policy work 03; staff mtg post-layoffs 03; CTL mtg report 03; BOD presentation 03; media 03; induced abortion/CTL mtg 03; logframes 03; MVA updates 03; Pakistan PPT 03; HIV/abortion 03; WHO presentation 03; US abortion overview 03; strat planning 03; org effectiveness 03; Addis unsafe abortion conf 03; repro rights presentation at GTZ -03; BOD presentations 03-04; MA 03-05; evaluating impact 03-05; donor presentations 03-08; training and equipping o4; MVA 04; I Shah presentation unsafe abortion conf 04; BOD presentation 04; remarks safe abortion workshop 04; DFID presentation 04; BOD presentation 04; sources of support 04; Nepal program 04; March for women's lives 04; remarks 04; results 04; PAC Cons. paper on MVA supply 04; MA partnership negotiations 05; Countdown 2015 Resources Working Group 05; Fred Nunes 05; MVA updates 05; MVA on-line 05; global MVA launch 05; remarks MVA launch 05; London press conf remarks 05; US program 05; presentations at BOD mtgs 05; sustainability 05; repro rights work 05; WUNC appeal 05; remarks Nairobi mtg 05 (Box 198)
  - Liz Maguire 05-07; B Crane remarks RH commodities mtg 05; remarks Ethiopia and AA receptions 05; Euro distributors workshop 05; Funders Network 05; Ethiopia remarks 05; advocacy messages 05; Ipas/AGI mtg DFID 05; legal reform benchmarks 05; Fathalla speech 05; strategy MDGs 05; advancing access/Eurodonors 05; paper on cost estimates 05; indicators; 05; visioning 05-06; MA 05-06; Ipas role in abortion technologies 05-09; MVA updates 06; staff chapters in AGI book 06; MVA 06; expanding reach presentation 06; Dick Gamble 06; policy session at CD mtg 06; background articles 06; assessment Ipas training capacity 06; remarks Brazil mtg 06; overview Ipas research 06; policy unit 06; Brazil trip 06; Rosa event 06; CDs presentation 06; DFID report 06; strat visioning for 07-11 in 06; SIDA visit 06; comments to foundation 06; BOD mtg presentations 06; Bixby presentation 06; remarks at Finance Comm 06; A Rosenfield tribute 06; 3 yr planning 06; Nigeria programs and partners 06-09; NORAD 06-09; Finland ministry presentation 07; experts mtg 07; Maputo 07; South Africa TOP conf speech 07; SOGON mtg – M Luke 07; BOD mtg presentations 07; tracking results 07-08; SIDA/Finnish visit 07; org chart 07; MVA pricing 07; Kenya trip 07; MA 07; Nicaragua 07-08; media material 07-08; Eurodonors 07-08; Belgium 07-08; CLAP mtg 07-09, 2005-2007 (Box 199)
  - Liz Maguire 08-11: MWIA Ghana presentation 08; Kenya abortion issues 08; vision progress report 08; remarks at conf on SH&R Nigeria 08; global mtg org improvement 08; press conf on safe abortion conf 08; MVA forecasting 08; India press 08; Africa Alliance 08; partners orgs 08; Ipas Nepal 08; Nigeria trip 08; Nica Rosita 08; remarks CDs mtg 08; remarks Ipas Delhi reception 08; global CDs mtg 08; MA 08; Making Abortions Safe in India conf 08; Women Deliver remarks 08; BOG mtg presentation 08; remarks global R&E mtg 08; DANIDA presentation 08; E Brookman-Amissah remarks at Safe Abortion conf 08; PSI 08—09; DKT 08-09; donor presentations 08-09; Ethiopia talks 08-10; MDA Global 09; abortion technologies strategy 09; Msg to LAC 09; Not Yet Rain premiere remarks 09; BOD mtg presentations 09; remarks global TSDI/PPD mtg 09; advocacy 09; Ipas Vietnam program summary 09; strat directions 09; presentations Women & AIDS conf 09; overview policy work 09; SAC strategies presentations 09; WomanCare Global announcement 09; agenda Strategic Alliances with Int'l NGOs mtg 09; Making the Case reports 09; AIDS conf sessions 09; Ipas policy on USAID funding 09; remarks Global Health Conf 09; strat planning 09; remarks Network of Women's Associations 09; global financial crisis 09; RA1 cost model study 09; Making the Case for US family planning assistance 09; Gag Rule 09; Ethiopia program 09; EngenderHealth/Ipas mtg 09; SIDA visit 09; Canada 10; Denmark funding 10; SIDA auditors 10; FIGO congress 10; Ltr to Lancet 10; SAF board 10; SIDA mtg 10; Dutch funding 10; remarks strat planning mtg 10; DFID mtgs and review 10; remarks Anon 2 workshop 10; org chart 10; remarks logframe workship 10; remarks Women Deliver 10; remarks staff party 10; remarks CD mtg 10; youth strategy 10; Ipas Africa overview 10; maternal mortality estimates 10; misc remarks 10; ICPD+15 NGOs 10; Ipas overview and org chart 10; WomanCare Global overview 10; NORAD 10-11; SAAF Board mtgs 10-11; PMDUP 11; core indicators 11; tribute to Rob Hogan 11; MDGs 11; US restrictions on funding 11; org restructuring 11; remarks/presentations 11; Kenya/DFID 11; MA at BOD mtg 11; Duke Archives agreements 11; remarks Ghana unsafe abortion mtg 11; strat planning for 12-16 in FY11; Personnel Comm 11; SIDA 11; USAID censor Malawi 11; re-org presentation 11; UNCPD 11; Germany 11, 2008-2011 (Box 200)
  - Liz Maguire: Four notebooks: Presentations 99-09, Presentations 10-15; Presentations to Board 99-03; Presidents Messages and presentations to Board 04-09; Three notebooks: RH Technologies 99-14; Messages to staff 99-09; Presentations to Ipas donors 04-14, 1999-2014 (Box 204-205)
  - Liz Maguire: SAAF 11; Eurodonors 12; remarks to staff 12; tribute to A Leonard 12; board presentations 12; improving provider/site performance 12; SAAF 12; WomanCare Global 12; conflict resolution 12; Intl FP conf 12; DFID review 12; women of courage 12; Clinton Global Initiative 12; core indicators 12; Ipas overview 12; Presidents' messages to Ipas Board 12 Core donor reports 12, 2011-2012 (Box 233)
  - Barbara Crane: Crane and Finkel interviews on population and family planning policies, 1970s-1980s. (Box 213)
  - Barbara Crane: Crane interviews, 1970s-1980s (Box 214)
  - Barbara Crane: Reproductive health topics, 1973-1991. Catholic views 73-80s, abortion research notes – Henry David 73-90; Catholic church – Papal and other official statements 74-80s; WHO – abortion 75-91; Anti-abortion literature 80s; abortion – int'l assistance 81-89; Opposition 82-90; abortion-related interviews 84-88; UNFPA – abortion 85-89; NRLC 86-90; IWHC 87-89; Pop Council – abortion 87-89; Abortion in Indonesia 88-90; FP/fertility paper 89; Bangladesh report 89; APHA – abortion 89-91; Crane paper outline 90; IFARH proposal 90; Transnational abortion politics paper 90; Sexuality background 90-91; abortion initiatives corres 90-91; Crane and Ipas 91. (Box 215)
  - Barbara Crane: Abortion and RH Topics, 93-09. Abortion/contraception/fertility transition 91-93; CEDAW 93; population 93-94; population/environment 93-94; Ethics, religion/RH 93-94; Coercion 93-94; Crane abortion politics paper 94; EC 94-04; Opposition 96; Mid-levels/Abortion 96; Gender 97; Repro rights 97; RH supplies/shortages 99; Russia RH 00; COBAC 00-01; Men and abortion 01-04; Refugees 01-05; Violence 01-05; HIV/AIDS/abortion 01-14; Adolescent Working Group 02-03; abortion attitudes 02-06; abortion values/ethics 04-07; adolescents/abortion 05; Marie Stopes 05; abortion costs 05-06; youth initiatives 06-07; refugees 07-09; report on women's health 09. (Box 216)
  - Barbara Crane: USAID and US population policy, 67-00. Pop policy background 67-91; USAID pop policy 82-91; USAID 73-88; USAID/State Dept/White House statements 84-85; Pop foreign policy 88-94; USAID STD report 92; USAID pop strategy 92; USAID gender working group 92-93; Jacobson statement 92-93; White paper – beyond Mexico City 93; Beilenson-Morella act 93; UNFPA/China news reports 93-94; US policy pre-ICPD 93-94; USAID misc comms 93-95; USAID pop overviews 93-00; China – USAID/UNFPA 94; CAs mtg 94; USAID 94; Liz Maguire's USAID presentations 94-96; USAID pop policy 94-99; USAID feminism article 95; RH Task Force USAID/PHN 95; Misc pop policy & RH reports/articles 93-99; MAQ conf 98; PD-3 USAID 98;USAID 98-99; Tiahrt notes 99-00; USAID/PHN comms 99-00 (Box 217)
  - Barbara Crane: ICPD – box 1 – 93-94 USAID/ICPD background; ICPD Prep Comm mtgs (2 folders); Prep Comm media; Prep Comm – non-AID submissions; Prep Comm – US interventions/key documents; ICPD prep; ICPD lead-up; US delegates mtg; ICPD NGO plans; ICPD inter-agency working group; Vatican/Catholics ICPD; ICPD definitions; ICPD preparations/consultative status; USAID/ICPD; U.S. preparatory documents; USAID – ICPD participant funders; USAID participants; USAID briefing book (Box 218)
  - Barbara Crane: ICPD – box 2 – 94-00 ICPD – U.S. positions and reference documents 94; ICPD and religion 94; ICPD – pop stabilization goals 94; ICPD environmental caucus 94; ICPD press/media 94; statements/remarks at ICPD 94; ICPD misc cables/statements 94; ICPD- cable responses/regional perspectives 94; USAID daily summaries 94; ICPD program/info/delegations 94; ICPD outcomes 94-95; ICPD follow-up – USAID and Dept of State 95; post ICPD summaries/follow-up 95-99; post ICPD follow-up 95-00 (Box 219)
  - Barbara Crane: ICPD Media. Newspaper/magazine articles on ICPD meeting in Cairo 1994 (Box 220)
  - Barbara Crane: Beijing, UNCPD/CSA, ICPD+5, ICPD+10, ICPD+15 – 95-10. Fourth World Conf on Women in Beijing 95; ICPD+5 – two folders 99; ICPD+5 – U.S. positions 99; ICPD+5 – UN review 99; UNCPD 02; UNCPD 03; UNCPD – actors and politics 04; UNCPD reference/background 04; UNCPD – Ipas initiatives 04; ICPD+10 05; ICPD+10 – advocacy 05; "From Controversy to Consensus on Abortion" mtg notebook 05; UN General Assembly mtg 05; UNCPD 05; UNCPD background 09; UNCPD documents 09; UNCPD statements 09; UNCPD panel 09; ICPD+15 09-10 (Box 221)
  - Barbara Crane: FIGO 00-12. FIGO 00 (two folders); FIGO 00-06; FIGO 03 (two folders); FIGO 06 (two folders); FIGO 07 (two folders); FIGO planning for 09; pre-Congress FIGO 09; FIGO 09 (two folders); `FIGO/ECSAOGS 09; FIGO Unsafe Abortion Working Group 09-15; FIGO 11 (two folders); FIGO 12; FIGO 12 panels. (Box 222)
  - Barbara Crane: Conferences/meetings/projects 87-03. Better Health through FP conf 87; PAA mtg 88; UN/IUSSP mtg on int'l transmission of pop policy experience 88; Politics of Induced Fertility Change conf 90; From Abortion to Contraception mtg 90; Group on FP/Health/Well-Being mtg 90; Women's Perspectives on Fertility Regulation Technology mtg 92; PAA mtg 92; Women's Health Roundtable 92; IPPF FP Congress 92; Effective FP Programs mtg 92; World Health Assembly 92; Contraceptive Research Symposium 93; IUSSP mtg 93; Health & Development Policy Project 93-97; Berkeley Roundtable 94; Working Group on RH and FP mtg 94; UNFPA visit 95; Packard Foundation Pop Program 97-99; articles by Crane 95-01; FP/abortion 96; RH Panel 96; Safe Motherhood 97; Safe Motherhood 97-98; Pop Comms Planning mtg 99; Working Group RH & FP 99; IWG mtg 01; APHA and PAC Consortium 01; professional advocacy 01; EuroNGOs presentation 01; Ipas strategic assessment 01; Safe Motherhood mtg 02 (two folders); maternal health research 02-05; Unsafe Abortion mtg 03; Safe Motherhood partnership 03-04. (Box 223)
  - Barbara Crane: Conferences/meetings/projects 04-12. March for Women's Lives 04; Safe Motherhood 04-05; DFID research 04-05; trip reports 04-06; Safe Motherhood/Newborn Health (SMNH) mtg 05; WUNC refusal 05; APHA 05; SMNH partnership mtg 05; SMNH global mtg 05; Gates mtg presentation 05; Funders Network Advocacy mtg 05; E Brookman-Amissah Philanthropy Forum 05; ARMM cost conf 05; Innovation in Supporting Local Health Systems for Global Women's Health symposium 05; CEDAW 07; Safe Motherhood PMNCH mtg 06; Campaign for MDGs 08; Women Deliver 08; Women Deliver 10; AJRH/Okonofua 10; PMNCH mtg 11; Int'l FP Conf in Dakar 12; CAC global network 12; FP Summit 12-13. (Box 224)
  - Barbara Crane: PAC, USAID PAC, MVA Drawdown. PAC 93-96; CAs PAC 94; PAC 95-00; MVA Drawdown 97-98; PAC Working group 98; PAC workshop 99; USAID PAC eval 01-02; PAC curriculum 02; mid-levels PAC 03; MVA drawdown 03-04; MVA supply 04; USAID PAC strategy 05; USAID PAC 05-06; USAID and MVA Drawdown 05-06; USAID PAC panel report 06; USAID PAC 07; USAID PAC workshop 07; USAID MVA for PAC 07. (Box 225)
  - Barbara Crane: Guttmacher, Africa Research Consortium, mid-level providers 05-08. AGI/Ipas bid to DFID 05; AGI/Ipas research partnership 04-05; research consortium concept/proposals 05-06; Africa Research Consortium 06; Consortium mtg and follow-up 06 (two folders); research consortium 09-10; Africa regional conf on unsafe abortion 11; IHCAR/WHO mid-level providers 00-02; ICM 02, ICM/midwives 08 (Box 226)
  - Barbara Crane: WHO 01-11. WHO Programme of Research, Development and Research Training in Human Reproduction 01; WHO mtg on unsafe abortion 01; WHO guidance mtg 01; trip report 01; WHO guidance 01-04; WHO 02-05; WHO relations 03-04; World Health Assembly 04; WHO medical abortion 05-06; WHO 05-09; WHO HRP 09; WHO/HRP mtg reports and docs 08-10; WHO/HRP mtg 11. (Box 227)
  - Barbara Crane: Medical Abortion 86-06. RU486 86-91; Antiprogestin drugs mtg 92; Misoprostol 01-04; MA research 06; MA/continuum of carr 01-06. (Box 228)
  - Barbara Crane: MVA 98-10 MVA San Fran workshop 98; MVA briefing papers 99-03; Bob Gillespie 00-03; UNFPA RH commodity mtg 01; Bob Gillespie 01-02; MVA launch 02-06; Nordic SRHR conf 03; MVA Drawdown 03-07; Bob Gillespie 03-06; Bellagio Technologies workshop 04; MVA access plan 04; Campbell 04; Speidel 04; Drawdown 04; UNPFA/MVA 05; MVA Access Plan 05; Rogo technologies article 05; Stockholm RH supplies 05; MVA launch 05; Potts 05; MVA on-line 05-06; MVA Vietnam 06; MVA Kenya Campbell 06; MVA consultant reports 06-07; Drawdown 07-08; MVA 07-08; MVA 07-10; WomanCare Global 09-10; abortion technologies/MA 09-10, 1998-2010 (Box 235)
  - Barbara Crane: Eurodonors 01-11 Early Eurodonors 01-03; Eurodonors 02-07; Eurodonors 06; DFID 00-02; DFID 02-04; DFID 06; DFID 06-07; DFID 09-10; DFID mtg 10; DFID Africa 10; DFID 11-12; Germany 11; Finland 03-08; Finland/Sweden 04; Denmark/Finland 01-07; Finland visit 07; Sida India 03-05; Sida proposal 04; Sida 06; Stockholm Sida 06; Sida 07; Sida proposal 06; Sida 07; Sida visit 07; Sida global 07-09; Sida visit 09; Sida Africa 09; Sida 09; Sida 09; Netherlands 00-02; Netherlands/UK trip 01; Netherlands 03; Netherlands 03; Netherlands extension report 04; Netherlands report material 05-06; Netherlands visit 06; Netherlands 07; Netherlands 08; Netherlands SALID mtg 09; Oslo 06; NORAD core report 08; Norway 08; NORAD SRHR expert mtg 10; Norway 11, 2001-2011 (Box 237)